Register to The Ernest Trow Carter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music by Carter, 1879-1968; Series I; 13.75' (33 boxes)
  - Chamber and Instrumental Works, I.G
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso] Largo Lamentoso: for String Quartet., 1 manuscript score ([8] p.); 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 332)
      Note on title page: Old Score - N.G.
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso] Largo lamentoso: for String Quartet., 1 manuscript score ([8] p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 332)
      Pencil sketches laid in and at end
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso] 2nd Movement: Larghetto Lamentoso: from String Quartet in G-major / Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1934 Aug. 31., 1 manuscript score (7 p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 332)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso] ca. 1908 Feb. 7., 17 manuscript parts; 5-34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 333)
      Holographs and manuscript in copyist's hand in ink
      Bottom left corner of most of the parts contains the above date and note: Old- N.G.- no cut
      Note on envelope: Odd parts of Larghetto and Minuet (not revised for MacDowell Club Dec. 1939)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso] Larghetto lamentoso / by Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1916-1939., 28 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 334)
      Holographs and manuscript in Otto Fessler's hand in ink
      Dates from bottom left corners of title pages
      Includes duplicates
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso; arr.] Larghetto Lamentoso: 2nd Movement of String Quartet in G: score with Bass ad libitum / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 335)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso; arr.] Larghetto Lamentoso: from String Quartet in G-major: Arranged for Violin, Cello, and Organ / by Ernest Carter. -- 1936., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 336)
      Note on title page: new 1936
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso; arr.] Larghetto Lamentoso: from String Quartet in G-major: Arranged for Violin, Cello, and Organ / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 336)
      Holograph, in ink with pencil additions
      Notes on title page: use for violin + cello: not organ, only for laying out; (old: penciled for new)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso; arr.] 3 manuscript parts; 33 cm., Holographs, signed, in ink (Box 30, Folder 336)
      Includes violin, violoncello, and organ parts
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso; arr.] Larghetto Lamentoso: from String Quartet in G-major; Arranged for Violin, Cello, and Piano / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (6 p.) + 3 parts; 33 cm. (Box 30, Folder 337)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Larghetto lamentoso (Sketches)] String Quartet / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 338)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet] 3rd Movement: Minuet from String Quartet in G-major / Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1934 Jun. 18., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 339)
      Date from bottom left corner of first p.
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet] Minuet / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([4] p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 339)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet] ca. 1908-1939., 29 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 340)
      manuscript in Otto Fessler's hand and holographs, signed, in ink
      Bass parts from arrangement laid in
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet; arr.] Minuet: for String Quartet / Ernest Carter. -- ca. 1908-1916., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 341)
      Arr. for string quartet with optional bass
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet; arr.] 3rd Movement of String Quartet in G: Minuet for String Quartet (Bass ad lib) / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 341)
    - [Quartets, strings, no. 1, G major. Minuet; arr.] ca. 1907-1934., 4 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 30, Folder 341)
      manuscript and holograph, signed, in ink
      Miscellaneous viola, violoncello, and 2 bass parts with various dates
    - [Rag-time bugle march; arr.] Rag-Time Bugle March: for Regimental Band and Bugle Corps: (arranged for Piano with Bugle or Cornet obligato) / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score (10 p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 342)
    - [Rag-time bugle march; arr.] Rag-Time Bugle March: for Regimental Band and Bugle Corps.: (arranged for piano with bugle or cornet obligato) / by Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 342)
    - [Romance, horn, strings (Sketches)] Romance for horn and strings., [1] sheet of music; 31 cm. (Box 30, Folder 343)
    - [Schottische and Galop] Schottische + Galop: (Triple tongued solo for B cornet) / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript part; 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 344)
      Cornet part
    - [Steps song; arr.] Steps Song: For Horn Quartette / Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([2] p.) + 8 parts; 32 cm. (Box 30, Folder 345)
      Includes 2 sets of parts
    - [Steps song; arr.] Steps Song: Arranged for String Quartet / by the composer Ernest Carter., 1 manuscript score ([3] p.); 32 cm. (Box 30, Folder 345)
    - [Unidentified piece, cornet, piano (Sketches)] Ernest Carter., [5] p. of music; 34 cm. (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - Sketches and Sketchbooks, I.H
    - [Selections (Sketches)] Kontrapunkt. -- 1886-1896., [96] p. of music, bound; 25 x 34 cm. (Box 31, Folder 347)
      Holographs in pencil and ink
      Pencil sketch on back cover
    - [Selections (Sketches)] 1887-1910., [38] p. of music, bound; 26 x 34 cm. (Box 31, Folder 348)
      Pencil sketch ([1] sheet; 13 x 21 cm.) laid in for "At the Lamb's high feast we sing," dated: Easter Apr. 6 '90
    - [Selections (Sketches)] Theory. -- 1896-1897., [79] p. of music, bound; 26 x 33 cm. (Box 31, Folder 349)
      Sketch on back cover and [7] p. of sketches laid in
    - [Selections (Sketches)] 1897 Feb. - May., [47] p. of music, bound; 25 x 33 cm. (Box 31, Folder 350)
    - [Selections (Sketches)], [10] p. of music; 23-35 cm. (Box 31, Folder 351)
      Holographs, in part signed, in pencil and ink (in part, photocopies)
      One sketch dated: 1908 Apr. 21
  - Carmina Princetonia, I.I
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1887)] Carmina Princetonia: the University Songbook: a collection of student songs as sung at Princeton College. - Sixth edition / editorial committee: E.T. Carter, George E. Shea, D. Hunter McAlpin, Jr. -- Newark, N.J.: Martin R. Dennis & Co., 1887, 93 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 352)
      Includes music by and arranged by Carter
      Ink sketch ([1] sheet; 12 x 26 cm.), "Where the chamiso and the edleweis make this home dwell," laid in
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1890)] Carmina Princetonia: the University Song Book. - Seventh edition. -- Newark, N.J.: Martin R. Dennis & Co., 1890., 125 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 353)
      Includes music by and arranged by Carter.
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1890)] Carmina Princetonia: the University Song Book. - Supplementary seventh edition. -- Newark, N.J.: Martin R. Dennis & Co., 1890., 125 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 353)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1894)] Carmina Princetonia: the University Song Book. - Eighth edition. Supplementary. -- Newark, N.J.: Martin R. Dennis & Co., 1894., 157 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 354)
      Two copies, one in poor condition with Carter's markings
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1898)] Carmina Princetonia: The University Song Book. - Ninth edition. -- Newark, N.J.: Martin R. Dennis & Co., 1898., 162 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 355)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1902)] Carmina Princetonia: The University Song Book. - Tenth edition. -- New York: G. Schirmer, 1902., 176 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 31, Folder 356)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1907)] Carmina Princetonia; The University Song Book. - Thirteenth edition / Edited by Ernest Carter, '88. -- New York: G. Schirmer, 1907., 192 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 32, Folder 357)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1910)] Carmina Princetonia: The University Song Book. - Fourteenth edition / Edited by Ernest Carter, '88. -- New York: G. Schirmer; Boston: Boston Music Company, 1910., 196 p.of music; 25 cm. (Box 32, Folder 358)
      Two copies, one copy includes pencil markings by Carter [for 15th ed., 1912?]
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1912)] Carmina Princetonia: The University Song Book. - Fifteenth edition / Edited by Ernest Carter, '88. -- New York: G. Schirmer; Boston: Boston Music Company, 1912., 211 p. of music; 25 cm. (Box 32, Folder 359)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1914)] Carmina Princetonia: The Princeton Song Book. - Eightheenth edition / Edited by a University Committee, Ernest Carter, '88, Chairman. -- New York: G. Schirmer; Boston: The Boston Music Co., c1914., [169] p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 32, Folder 360)
      Contains markings and additions by Carter
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1934)] Carmina Princetonia: The Princeton Song Book. - Tweny-forth issue / Edited by a University committee, Ernest Carter, '88, Chairman. -- New York: G. Schirmer, c1934., [169] p. of music; 27 cm. (Box 32, Folder 361)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1940)] Carmina Princetonia: The Princeton Song Book. - Twenty-fifth issue / Edited by a University Committee, Ernest Carter, '88, Chairman. -- New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1940., 207 p. of music; 27 cm. (Box 32, Folder 362)
    - [Carmina Princetonia (1968)] Carmina Princetonia: The Songbook of Princeton University. - Centennial Edition / Edited by a University committee with biographical sketches of alumni authors and composers. -- New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1968., 186 p. of music; 27 cm. (Box 32, Folder 363)
      Two copies: advertisement for this edition and clipping laid in one copy; typed letter signed from G. Schirmer to Carter, with Carter's reply, laid in the other copy
- Music Arranged by Carter, 1898-1946; Series II; .4' (1 box)
  This series includes manuscript and published music by others arranged by Carter. The music is arranged alphabetically by composer or title. Uniform titles are used to bring together all of the manifestations of a work with various titles. Cross references appear in the index for those pieces which are included with another work. Folders are numbered consecutively throughout the series.
- Music by Others, 1902-1909; Series III; .4' (1 box)
  This series includes manuscript and published music by others. It is arranged alphabetically by composer or title. Uniform titles are used to bring together all the manifestations of a work within various titles. Cross references appear in the index between music by others in this series and the corresponding arrangements by Carter in Series II. Folders are numbered consecutively throughout the series.
- Production Materials, 1907-1946; Series IV; .8' (2 boxes)
  Production materials include holograph, manuscript, and typescript scenarios, stage directions, sketches for stage plans, timetables of musical numbers, notes, and records of materials and costs. Also included are lists of costumes, musical numbers, characters, properties, tempi, musical themes, rehearsal numbers, lighting, cast, and rehearsal numbers. There are three subseries (A-C) for Carter's stage works: The Blonde Donna; Namba; and The White Bird. Boxes and folders are numbered consecutively throughout the series, with the exception of oversized material, which is housed at the end (Box 44).
  - Blonde Donna, IV.A
    - Miscellaneous scenarios, one in German, 1912-1941; 14 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Typescripts, in part with pencil additions, and manuscript in ink
    - Lists of musical numbers, characters, and other notes, ca. 1907-1946; 11 items; 9-34 cm. (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Holographs and manuscript in ink, and typescripts with pencil additions
      Two lists in German
    - Stage directions, no date; 3 items; 28-33 cm. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Holographs in ink and pencil, and typescript
    - Timetables of musical numbers, no date; 8 items; 20-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Holographs in pencil and typescripts with pencil additions
    - Notes concerning scores and parts, ca. 1936 Jan. 20; 10 items; 18-32 cm. (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Holographs in ink and pencil, and typescripts with pencil additions
    - Lists of costumes, 1937 Jul. 1; 14 items; 15-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Holographs and manuscript in pencil, and typescripts with pencil and ink additions
    - Lists of properties, no date; 12 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Typescripts, in part with pencil additions
    - Sketches for stage plans, ca. 1931-1941; 6 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Manuscript in pencil and photocopies
  - Namba, IV.B
    - Scenarios, no date; 3 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Lists of musical rehearsal numbers, cast, and orchestra parts, 1933 Apr. 22; 4 items; 17-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Holographs in ink and typescripts
    - Stage directions, 1933-1934; 10 items; 18-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Holograph in pencil, manuscript in ink, and typescripts with pencil and ink additions
    - Sketches for properties, no date; 5 items; 23-52 cm. (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Manuscript in pencil
  - White Bird, IV.C
    - Scenarios, no date; 5 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Stage directions, no date; 5 items; 14-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 13)
      Holographs in ink and typescript with pencil additions
    - Lists of approximate tempi, no date; 4 items; 28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 14)
      Holographs in pencil and typescripts with pencil and ink additions
    - Lists of musical themes and numbers, characters, and orchestra parts., 1919-1930; 40 items; 14-39 cm. (Box 34, Folder 15)
      Also included are a notebook with sketches of stage settings, a sheet recording materials and costs for stage setting by Willis J. Physioc, and miscellaneous notes
      Holographs in ink and pencil, and typescripts, in part with pencil and ink additions
    - Lists and sketches of properties, costumes, stage settings, and lighting, 1937-1939; 36 items; 8-28 cm. (Box 34, Folder 16)
      Holographs and manuscripts in pencil and ink, typescripts, negative and positive photocopies, and printed items
- Correspondence, 1894-1951; Series V; .8' (2 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The correspondence is divided into three subseries: A. From Carter; B. To Carter; and C. Between Others. The majority of the letters from Carter are typescript copies. These have been copied onto acid-free paper, and only those original letters which are either signed by Carter or contain his notes remain in the collection. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by recipient or sender, except for the last subseries, which is arranged chronologically. Boxes and folders are numbered consecutively throughout the series. Cross-references appear among the entries. Many letters to Carter contain enclosures or Carter's sketches for his replies on the backs, and notes appear when this occurs.
  - Correspondence from Carter, V.A
    - Armacost, Dr., 1949 Jul. 10; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Barrie, Helen, 1933 Apr.-May; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Bartholomew, Marshall, 1924 Jun. 2; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Bauer, Emily Frances, 1924-1933; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Bevans, George Esdras, 1950 Jan.-May; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Borowsky, Serge, 1939 Aug. 16; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Boyd, Julian P., 1949 Nov. 23; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Briggs, Ernest, 1940 Aug. 14; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Brown, William
      see United States. Library of Congress. Copyright Office.
    - Bruchhausen, Carl, 1922 May 16; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Burke, John E., 1931 May-Nov.; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau, Inc., 1933 Jan. 5; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - [Cantrell?], Barton, 1939 Jul. 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Alan, 1933-1949; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Laura, 1915 Jul. 11; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Polly, Betty, and Roger, 1939-1949; 10 items (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Carter, ? [Carter's mother], 1924 Mar. 2; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Chalmers, Thomas, 1922 Jun. 8; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Kenneth S., 1939 Dec. 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Craft, Marcella, 1939-1949; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Crist, Wilbur. E., 1940 Mar.-Dec.; 5 items (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Crooks, ? [Mr.], 1922 Aug. 29; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Cutter, James Bird, 1941-1949; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Damrosch, Walter, no date; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - DeVoe, Elsie, 1924 Jan. 26; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Devries, Herman, 1924 Mar. 17; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dippel, Andreas, 1914 Nov. 20; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - DiSalle, Frederick, 1933 Mar. 13; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dodds, Harold. W., 1934 Jun.-Aug.; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Donaldson, ? [Mr.], 1920 Jan. 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dore, Aleta, 1933 Apr. 13; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Downes, Olin, 1928 Nov. 8; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Driggs, Spencer B., 1932-1933; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Duffield, Edward D., 1934 May-Jun.; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Fessler, Otto, 1924 Mar. 17; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Forsyth, Holmes, 1924 Mar. 9; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Fortier, Florestine (Mrs. Leopold), 1922 Aug.- Nov.; 5 items (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Foster, Bertha, 1949 Feb. 9; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Freer, Eleanor E. (Mrs. Archibald), 1922-1924; 47 items (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - French, Florence, 1922-1933; 8 items (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Frost, Bernice, 1933 May 4; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Furniss, Walter W., 1940 Dec. 4; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc., 1913-1929; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gallagher, Charles E., 1922 Oct. 19; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Garden, Mary, 1921-1922; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gatti-Casazza, Giulio, 1920 Apr. 20; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gerdau, Allan, 1927 Feb. 2; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Good, ? (Mrs. R. E.), 1924 Feb.-Mar.; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Gordon Musical Association, Inc., 1949 Jan. 29; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Granberry, George F., 1933 Jan. 6; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Grutzmacher, ? [Mrs.], 1927 Jan.-Mar.; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Guthrie, James K., 1942-1953; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Haskell, William S., 1921-1924; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Henderson, W. J., 1924 Feb. 13; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Herzog, Sigmund, 1920 Sep. 21-23; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Hibben, John Grier, 1923-1932; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Hinshaw, William Wade, 1921-1922; 6 items (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Hipsher, Edward Ellsworth, 1933 Jan. 31; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Hoe, Laura, 1927-1940; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Hoe, Robert, 1927 Feb. 24; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Homaus, Loraine, 1923 Sep. 14; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Hooker, Brian, 1920-1942; 11 items (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Hubbard, ? [Mrs.], 1922 May 25; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Isaacson, Charles D., 1921 May 12; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Jamison, ? [Mr. and Mrs.], 1949 Jul. 24; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Jillson, David C., 1931 Nov. 24; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Horace, 1924 Mar. 24; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Charles T. H., 1923-1927; 20 items (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Jones, M. Edith, 1924 Feb.-May; 10 items (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Judson, Arthur, 1924 Mar.-Apr.; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Kahn, Otto H., 1919-1924; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Keith, John S., 1924 Apr. 10-27; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Kneisel, Marianne, 1933 Jun. 22; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 15)
      Enclosure
    - Knight, John
      see Players, The
    - Kraeuter, ? [Mr.], 1940 Dec. 5; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - LeMassena, C.E., 1922 May 26; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Liebscher, ? [Mr.], 1927 Sep. 1; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Linn, Katharine C., 1922 May 26; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Lund, Charlotte, 1933 Mar.-Apr.; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - M. Whitmark & Sons, 1943 Dec. 29; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Madden, Myrtle R., 1923 Dec. 14; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - McCay, Leroy W., 1922 May 15; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - McClure, Grace (Mrs. C. F. W.), 1922-1937; 25 items (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - [McClure?], Spot (Grace McClure's dog?), 1933 Mar. 17; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - [McClure?], Mac, 1933 Apr. 9; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - McCormick, Cyrus H., 1921-1924; 5 items (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - McCormick, (Mrs. Harold F.), 1922 Feb. 16; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 18)
      2 enclosures
    - Mackay, Clarence H., 1922 Mar. 3; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Martens, Frederick H., 1924 Apr. 21-30; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Marvin, Dwight, 1948 May 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1935 Apr. 22; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Michaelis, Emil B., 1933 Jan.-Apr.; 5 items (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Montgomery, James S., 1920 Jan. 30; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Moore, Edward, 1924 Mar. 11; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Mullen, Grace Stewart (Mrs. George E.), 1942-1949; 14 items (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Musical Courier, 1949 May 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Musical Digest, 1933 May 10; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Music News
      see DeVoe, Elsie
    - Mussey, Kendall, 1931 May 18; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Nevin, Arthur, 1924 Feb. 17-21; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - New York Opera Comique, 1931 Nov.-Dec.; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - New York Times, 1922 Jan. 23-24; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
      Includes several drafts
    - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1922 May 16-22; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Osnabrück Theater Orchestra, 1927 Nov. 15; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Outlook, 1924 Dec. 5; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Panenko, Antonio, 1931 Oct.-Nov.; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Patton, [Fred] L., 1901-1922; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Phillips, Howard C., 1924 Feb. 8; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Polacco, [Maestro], 1924 Apr. 12; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Pratt, ? [Mr.], 1949 Aug. 13; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Rice, Edwin T., 1922 Oct.-Nov.; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Richards, Elizabeth L., 1937-1943; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 24)
      Enclosures
    - Rimond, Hofrath, 1927 Apr.-May; 31 items (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Ross, Walter W. (Charlie), 1924 Jan. 14; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Russell, ? [Mr.], 1921 Mar. 4; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - S.L. Hutchinson & Vogt, Inc., 1941 Jul. 28; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Sam S. & Lee Shubert, Inc., 1922 Feb. 2; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Shea, George Edward, 1922 Jun. 21; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Sheldon, Harriet, 1924 Jan. 29; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Shelton, Mary Ellen, 1949 Jun.-Jul.; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Evelyn French, 1942-1949; 3 items (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Harry B., 1908 Mar. 3; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Stephan, Walter G., 1922 Oct. 11; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Stidham, ? [Mr.], 1943 Mar. 26; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Swaab, M.B., 1933-1949; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Talbot, Bryce, 1924 Mar. 12-22; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Taylor, Deems, 1922-1924; 2 items (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Theodore Presser Co., 1924 Jul. 1; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Thomas, Rudolph, 1931 Nov.-Dec.; 4 items (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence, 1935 Jan. 4; 1 item (Box 35, Folder 26)